The house that really stands out is a house located on Jelen Rynek 24, in Poland.
There are many stories about the house and no one knows the real source of the evil that is there.
Other families left the house very quickly.
Within 10 years, more than 30 families have moved out.
That's right, no one has stayed for so long.
Around 1940, a house is being built for a family and their two children.
As soon as they moved in, the parents began to argue.
It even goes so far that the father in the family abuses the wife and the children.
Time passes and after a couple of years the children disappear under mysterious circumstances.
A rumor is spread in the village, that it is the father who has murdered the children and that they are buried in the basement.
The parents flee the country and during a house search, bloody tools are found in the basement.
But the remains from the children were never found.
In 1961, a new family moved into the house.
Those who have now moved in are starting to call the police that strange phenomena are starting to happen in the house.
They hear how someone goes in the wind, things are thrown into the rooms where no one is and the daughter in the family screams in the middle of the night, which wakes up the whole family.
When the parents go into her daughter's room, she floats above her bed.
It went so far that the Catholic Church sent priests to the house, to implement an exorcism.
Despite attempts to clean the house, no one has managed to get it completely calm.
We have now been around and tried to interview people, Simon has helped.
Are the stories correct?
We have tried as best we can, not many people want to be with unfortunately.
So I still think we have got very good things from those who are here in the immediate area.
So exciting to see what happens here tonight.
Then we are here in the Poltergeist house here in Poland.
We also have here and did a live, it can be seen on the website.
We recognize this house, we have been here before with ghost hunting, much happened then.
Danjal was drawn in the leg, bangs in the house and things that are thrown.
So there is a lot going on and is said to happen here.
Over 30 families say they have moved away.
And earlier today, very interesting, we got through Theodor during our live broadcast from here.
And a witness outside, an older man, talks about that there were two Theodor here.
A father named Theodor and he named his son to Theodor Jr.
So we had to confirm that very quickly.
He could also tell you that an exorcism has been performed here in the house, so there is also confirmed and it is super interesting for the evening.
It's time to go in, the surveillance cameras are ready.
We will test different sessions, we have with Simon from Poland that will translate some Polish words that come through.
Mixed sessions, we will go through basements and up to the wind.
But we will first go here in the Bo part itself.
We go in.
As I said we were here and drove a live and it feels ..
It feels different in the house, I don't know how to say.
Now there is a lot through here.
Theodor is it you who murdered your children?
Now I get back pain, it jumped from here up to the left shoulder.
It's like I've been a camera for a long time.
Now it is starting to ache in the entire spine, as it takes energy from one.
I asked about this with the kids.
Did you stroll your children?
I think we put PRP here.
Stir the antenna.
Immediately when I said it I start to shudder, it gets cold on my back.
Do it?
Shit what i shudder ...
Throw down that cross if you don't believe.
I think we move on, we leave this room.
Now we are in the room where the radio was before, now it is removed.
But it was here before, in the corner.
What sounded?
Is that the floor?
It sounded like something bounced ...
The picture from the surveillance behaves strangely.
Show your power here now.
You have got so many families to escape from here.
The picture is slow and blurred.
Are you angry because we're here?
I have light dizziness, it spun at once.
Who are you?
Why are you here and why are you attacking people?
After all, you pushed down a person for the stairs here.
Why did you push him?
The picture is still slow and blurred.
So you mean he slipped?
It wasn't you who did it?
If it wasn't you who did it, knock once somewhere.
2 knocks and some strange sound.
Can you knock like this?
If you don't like Jesus symbol here, throw down the board.
Then release the picture again, could the house have done this so that we would not get anything on film at the board?
Every time I say it gets icy at my back.
It crawls a cold behind me ..
Forced boy.
It is a theory we think of, the dark that is here, it may have forced himself to the father Theodor, or the son, we do not really know which of them it is, to do things.
Did you get obsessed with something?
Have you flown on you?
Yes.
What came in here now?
Now you can also communicate with this flashing light, soon it will be blue.
Did you get obsessed with something?
Were there six people who became obsessed here?
After all, it is over thirty family who left here.
I'll just check out here quickly.
Throw some porcelain.
There is a lot of crunch here.
It is because we walk on the floor, it crackles all the time.
Each time you say something it crashes, but that's the floor.
And is a little calmer here so we get up to the wind.
If there is any child here, can you come in here and call the bell that is there?
Can we hear your voice?
You can come in and take in this iron stick or go to the light that flashes here
I start Ovilus too, see what it says to me.
The battery dropped quite quickly from 75 and now it stands at 66.
The figure 6 has been quite throughout here.
It may have been an ir light, otherwise you got a light phenomenon against you.
Or a reflection.
It may have been a reflection.
Should we test a theory only, we pull out the cable, we have a surveillance camera here ...
Sometimes there is more activity when it is not documented in the same way.
So we try pulling out the cable here.
So we see what happens.
I'm coming with.
I barely come here ..
Very strong.
If you back a little neighbor I can get closer to you.
There it backed, good!
It listens.
Do you notice that it directly follows your commands?
Is that Theodor?
Now it went behind you.
And then we got movement in that direction I think.
It really follows what you say.
Now I saw something, something white behind you.
A little further up the right.
I thought it was a human being.
The one who moves in here.
And you are at a point where we were before, so the whole house shook.
Right.
I am pulled away from here, I am drawn here.
We go well then then.
I relax this again.
We got well too.
We have received that before.
The theory is also that the children were thrown into a well covered with stone.
Give us a sign that you are up here with us now.
A loud sound would be very nice.
Or push us over.
Throw something.
Is this your doll?
"Yes, go"
Lennie, now we have changed a bit.
Tony went in with Simon in the car so you and I go in and then you have to run a paranormal puck.
I have this in my pocket.
Paranormal Puck 2. I also have the phone where we enter the questions.
We test everything possible here because we have contact with something dark in there.
So we'll see.
I put it down there.
We put the puck down on the instruments.
It will flash a little from your phone, but it's just the iPhone, they blink.
Now we all see dots there, it has nothing to do with this feature.
Should we start asking questions then Niclas?
Write and ask if Theodor is here.
Is Theodor here?
Memories of Theodor are here.
You can also say that, if it is a demon that has been here from the beginning.
After all, they have done exorcism here, so we are starting to understand that it is back here.
I know it goes down into the basement too.
There is a ground floor there, so you can interpret it as dirt maybe.
We have had that theory, but we also believe when we go down there, so we get nothing, but it is up here.
But if we say that everything has started down there, in the ground floor, it is not entirely impossible that the darkness has been projected from there.
And got into the building here.
For just in this room it is the greatest discomfort.
The wind is decent, but it is here.
You know most here I think.
Got no answer ..
Very interesting actually because it always comes through something.
When you asked that question, if something is buried in the dirt ... then it became nothing.
Almost as our theory is starting to match.
Maybe through the camera then.
Or the second surveillance camera.
I shiver.
Damn what I'm starting to shudder.
Damn cool!
I think if you should ask about something Christian ..
It is also damn exciting, if it would be.
They want us to think that it is a nun, something religious, but that there is something else that is trying to influence.
Then nothing likes the religious.
*What is being recorded now scares us*
*It is only Lennie and Niclas in the room, but a voice is recorded that laughs or growl to us.*
It was another voice!
What was that?
There was someone else who also laughed with us.
What the hell was Niclas?
It was another voice that laughed exactly at the same time as you.
So damn clear it was.
A real tan.
When we both laughed, it laughed with us.
No answer.
Now there is no more nun anymore.
When it called Jesus Christ witch.
Now I haven't even written anything and got to sneak.
And that means you sneak on someone.
Exactly.
And you didn't even write anything?
No nothing.
Okay.
But that was so damn uncomfortable.
Damn what uncomfortable.
That is why I want to drive with a microphone, because then we catch everything.
Had we had something else we would not have received it EVP.
It was clean!
It was another vote.
After all, we got a dark, dark voice through Ghostbox.
We go in there where the board and the cross are, bring you paranormal puck there.
We ask some questions there.
Something is moved in the kitchen.
Did you hear?
What was that?
What if it's a kind of portal?
I think it's damn uncomfortable for the kitchen now.
But it was porcelain that sounded.
We have previously asked if they can move something there.
It's like they're stuck there ...
So they keep them there in the basement, but I wonder why.
What they had to do here is to dig out at the bottom of the house.
See what they get there, if there are legs ...
If something binds some energies left to this house.
Should we test Kinect in here?
We can do that.
We go around here and see if we can get a mapping.
We have got good stuff on paranormal puck.
Really.
So we go and pick it up.
Do we have someone with us in this room?
Show yourself now!
Come into this room now.
Back to bed.
I stand here and look at the piano.
It's like it sneaks around ..
It does not want to show up in any way.
Should we test go in there?
I check if anyone is here in the kitchen.
There was something that sounded there at the mugs before.
Then we go into the room where we have a picture of Jesus.
And a cross.
That picture has flown down.
Says the owner.
Is there anyone with us in this room?
Strange, because it really feels like there is something here.
We have felt a discomfort.
If you back a little bit, we just hold it out here.
So we try to call in what is there.
No mapping here.
We have also tested the basement and the wind.
Should we test go up in the attic and check out?
Where!
From the piano.
The bed is.
It was like it lay there then it crawled out.
It is the first up the mapping we have here.
We try and get up.
At the doll!
Just like someone was sitting there.
Now it's nothing.
Now someone hangs above.
But it is something that is not right here, it is something that calls itself what it is not ..
It is so sneaky, first you look for it, then it disappears.
It's so sick.
Poltergeist The house in Poland really lives up to its expectations.
As soon as we arrive at the house, we get shivers throughout the body, something that everyone feels very strong.
Talking about Jesus or other Christian words, then the discomfort comes back immediately.
Maybe it is that the evil that once tried to be cleared away through exorcism is still there.
During the investigation, we received lots of words to indicate that the children's remains may remain in the basement.
The question is what to find if you start digging in the ground ...
What was clearly felt strongest, because we both heard and felt physically, is the entity that calls itself the nun Sally.
Is it she who stays and sucks in spirits and souls?
Or is it the house itself that keeps them locked up inside the walls of the house?
It seems that those who remain do not know why they are there.
Once again, we see the theory of not having all cameras going, works.
And that activity increases as we pull out one of the surveillance cameras.
We then got to experience phenomena that we have not experienced much anymore.
What is in the house has such power that it can even freeze the image on our monitoring system.
Just as it knows it is being documented.
We have never experienced this freezing of the picture during all our years as investigators.
In the attic we got through our SLS camera two pieces up mappings of energies.
Could this be Theodor or the children who wanted to show up for us?
If we sum up the investigation from the Poltergeist house, we can say that it was a long time we got to experience such strong phenomena during an investigation.
Getting the name Theodor that is highly topical for the house, as a former owner means that we came a step closer to who is still there.
But the darkness that rests over the place is something completely different.
It is a force that you should have great respect for when you are in the house.
You never know what it is capable of doing, but those who have the courage to visit the house, on Jelen Ryned 24 ..